<?xml version = "1.0" encoding = "UTF-8"?>
<gallery-images>
	<gallery-image data-name="SpragueLake-2018Sep8j">
		<image-title>On the north shore of Sprague Lake</image-title>
		<image-description>Near the end of a long night of shooting from the shores of Sprague Lake, I stumbled upon this composition and stopped abruptly as several stars, and even a hint of the Milky Way, were reflected in the calm water.</image-description>
	</gallery-image>
	<gallery-image data-name="MorainePark-2018Sep12-stack">
		<image-title>Late summer night in Moraine Park</image-title>
		<image-description>Less than 4 miles from downtown Estes Park, this image shot from Moraine Park exemplifies the community's efforts to minimize light pollution. The bright star left of the Milky Way is Mars. In the foreground, a hiker's headlamp lights the way on the East Longs Peak Trail.</image-description>
	</gallery-image>
	<gallery-image data-name="EastLongsPeakTrail-2018Sep22">
		<image-title>Front Range from the Keyhole Route</image-title>
		<image-description>On the East Longs Peak Trail, with a nearly full moon behind us, civilization on the Front Range glows in the distance. With all that light pollution, it's surprising to see the camera capture a hint of the Orion Nebula.</image-description>
	</gallery-image>
	<gallery-image data-name="FirsReaching-2018Sep8">
		<image-title>Firs reaching for the stars</image-title>
		<image-description>At Sprague Lake, this grove of trees seems to be pointing to the Milky Way and stretching toward the stars.</image-description>
	</gallery-image>
	<gallery-image data-name="GemLake-2019Jul28">
		<image-title>Estes Park from Gem Lake</image-title>
		<image-description>Looking southward from Gem Lake yields a nice view of Estes Park with Mount Meeker and Longs Peak behind. Somewhat farther to the south, the Milky Way competes for your attention.</image-description>
	</gallery-image>
	<gallery-image data-name="ForestCanyonOverlook-2020Jul19">
		<image-title>Midsummer night at Forest Canyon Overlook</image-title>
		<image-description>Looking southward from this spur off Trail Ridge Road yields a nice view of the Milky Way with Sprague Mountain and Stones Peak in the foreground.</image-description>
	</gallery-image>
	<gallery-image data-name="BierstadtLakeSoutheast-2021Jul9">
		<image-title>At Bierstadt Lake and looking southeast</image-title>
		<image-description>From the north shore of Bierstadt Lake, we get a view of the Milky Way with Long's Peak underneath and to the right.</image-description>
	</gallery-image>
	<gallery-image data-name="BierstadtLakeSouthwest-2021Jul9">
		<image-title>At Bierstadt Lake and looking southwest</image-title>
		<image-description>From the north shore of Bierstadt Lake, we get a nice view of the Milky Way with Long's Peak underneath and to the left. Wildfire smoke from California, Oregon and Washington is seen low on the horizon.</image-description>
	</gallery-image>
</gallery-images>
